myqnapcloud.com 2013-08-05

# Home

## QNAP Privacy Policy

QNAP takes your privacy seriously, this Privacy Policy covers your privacy rights regarding how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, store and protect your personal information .It applies to QNAP website and all related sites, applications, services and tools regardless of how you access or use them.

You accept this Privacy Policy when you sign up for, access, or use our products, services, content, features, technologies or functions offered on our website and all related sites, applications, and services (collectively ‘’QNAP Services’’).Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you

#### Policy of Information Collection and Use

QNAP may collect your personal information when using QNAP Services or in contact with us, We may collect a variety of information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, phone number, email address or your contact preferences. 

QNAP may use your personal information according to this Privacy Policy. QNAP may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. Here are some examples of the types of using your personal information:

  * We may use your personal information to keep you posted on QNAP’s latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events.
  * We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.
  * We may periodically use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with QNAP, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  * We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve QNAP’s products, services, and customer communications.
  * If you enter into a contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

#### Policy of Personal Information Sharing and Disclosure

QNAP does not share or disclose your personal information to other people or non-affiliated companies except your permission or under the following circumstances:

  * We share your personal information to our trusted service providers such as information processing, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys, that work on behalf or with QNAP . For example, when you purchase and activate your QNAP device, you authorize QNAP to exchange the information you provide during the activation process to carry out service. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by QNAP’s privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by QNAP to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. These service providers are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever QNAP operates.
  * We may also share your personal information with the financial institutions that we partner with to jointly create and offer QNAP Services or Banking partners as required by credit card association rules.
  * We disclose personal information necessary by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence or when the public interest is involved.
  * We may also disclose personal information in order to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users.
  * We transfer your personal information to the relevant third party if we are in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale.

#### Personal Information Security

Your personal information is kept secure by QNAP’s administrative, technical, and physical safeguards, avoiding your personal information from loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

#### Integrity and Retention of Personal Information

In order to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. Your personal information will be retained for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

#### Access to Personal Information

QNAP aims to ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at [https://www.myQNAPcloud.com.](https://www.myqnapcloud.com/)

For other personal information, QNAP provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data - unless we have to retain it for legitimate business or legal purposes. QNAP may reject your requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by law.

#### Third-Party Sites and Services

QNAP’s websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties − for example, a third-party QNAP app and Cloud services. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices and you are encouraged to review the privacy practices of those third parties. QNAP is not responsible for the content or information practices of such third parties.

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

QNAP will revise this Privacy Policy from time to time . Any revisions to this policy will be posted publicly.

#### Questions And Suggestions

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about our Privacy Policy or data processing, please [contact us](http://helpdesk.qnap.com/).
